[Music]
how you doing Franco you look like
Johnny Depp with lupus does Ryan Gosling
ever call you start laughing and then
hang up
[Applause]
Franco is half Italian and half asleep
[Laughter]
having a hand for James's grandma 91
years old
127 hours is how long she has left
get him grandma get him get him
Oh Franco Franco comes from humble
beginnings right your first job is
working at McDonald's the last time
anybody ever said about your work I'm
loving it and because you're an academic
I treated this roast like a research
project I watched all your films
I read your poetry I even have one of
your paintings hanging in my fire pit
you know Franco person I don't care if
you guys or girls all I know
is you me at a 12 bucks when I
went to see that Wizard of Oz movie
ultim I was in the theater I was
thinking there's no place like home
but Franco I'm really looking forward to
you mumbling your rebuttal at the end of
the show are you ready to bring it
Franco let's help you that's good let's
hope you bring some of that razor-sharp
wit you brought to the Oscars you are a
worse host in the aids monkey
[Music]